<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Top5HighestMountain</string>
    <string name="intro">Indonesia is the largest archipelago in the world and Most of Indonesia is mountainous. The Highest Mountains separated on the islands of Sumatra, Java, , Papua and NTB. The country\'s tallest mountains located in the Jayawijaya Mountains that has enternal SNOW.
    \n This app will bring you to the top 5 of Highest Mountains in Indonesia</string>

    <string name="title_activity_number1">number1Activity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="mtSanggar">Mt. Sanggar</string>
    <string name="id05">qcv6Q5zvRqI</string>
    <string name="desc_mtsanggar">Gunung Sanggar is a 3564 m or 11,431 ft mountain peak near Lelongken, NTB, Indonesia. Based on peakery data, it ranks as the 2nd highest mountain in Nusa Tenggara Barat and the 19th highest mountain in Indonesia.
        Gunung Sanggar is a mountain in the region of Jawa Barat, the country of Indonesia with an average elevation of 906 meter above sea level. The area is densely populated with 549 people per km2 . The nearest town larger than 50,000 inhabitants takes about 0:51 hour by local transportation.</string>
    <string name="mtsemeru">Mt. Semeru</string>
    <string name="mtrinjani">Mt. Rinjani</string>
    <string name="mtkerinci">Mt. Kerinci</string>
    <string name="mtcartenz">Mt. Cartenz</string>
    <string name="desc_mtsemeru">MountSemeru, is a volcano located in East Java, Indonesia. It is the highest mountain on the island of Java. The strato volcano is also known as Mahameru, meaning The Great Mountain. The name derived from Hindu-Buddhist mythical mountain of Meru or Sumeru, the abode of gods.</string>
    <string name="desc_mtrinjani">Mount Rinjani is a mountain located on the island of Lombok, West Nusa Tenggara. Mountain which is the second highest volcano in Indonesia with an altitude of 3726 m above sea level and lies in latitude 8 º 25 ‘latitude and 116 º 28’ BT is a favorite for mountain climbers Indonesia for its beautiful scenery. This mountain is part of Mount Rinjani National Park which has an area of about 41,330 ha and this will be proposed the addition to be 76 000 ha to the west and east. Administratively, the mountain is located in the territory of three districts: East Lombok, Central Lombok and West Lombok.</string>
    <string name="desc_mtkerinci">Kerinci mountain is located in Kerinci regency, Jambi Province. Kerinci mount is active vulcano, with an altitude of 3805 masl. The mountain is the highest mountain in Indonesia outside the mountains of Papua. In the east side is alakeBento, the highest clear watery swamps in Sumatra.</string>
    <string name="desc_mtjaya">At 4,884 metres or 16,024 ft above sea level, The peak name is Jayawijaya or Puncak Jaya which is the highest mountain in Indonesia, the highest on the island of New Guinea, the highest of Oceania , and the 5th highest mountain in political Southeast Asia. It is also the highest point between the Himalayas and the Andes, and the highest island peaks the world. There are several peak such as Puncak Trikora, Puncak Mandala, and Puncak Jaya.</string>
</resources>
